const quiz3data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "This is the bridge __ David built.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "that", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "who", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: '"That" is used to make clear which thing we are talking about. "Who" is used only for people.'
   },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "Daniel was not sure __ he could trust with his secret.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "which", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "whom", isCorrect: true}
      ],
      help: 'We use "whom" to refer to people when the person is the object of the verb.'
   },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "London, __ is a very beautiful city, is where my brother lives.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "which", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "that", isCorrect: false}
      ],
      help: 'We use "which" to give more information about a thing in a nonessential relative clause. '
   },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "The book __ is assigned to me is 500 pages.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "which", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "that", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'We use "that" to give more information about a thing in an essential relative clause.'
   },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "Alexander Fleming is the man __ discovered penicillin.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "who", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "which", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use "who" to make clear which person we are talking about.'
   },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "This is Juan, __ sister works with my brother.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "whom", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "whose", isCorrect: true}
      ],
      help: 'We use "whose" to indicate possession.'
   },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "My new car, __ was in park, was hit from behind.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "which", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "who", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use "which" to give more information about a thing in a nonessential relative clause.'
   },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "Emmanuel, __ is 65, has just retired.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "which", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "who", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'We use "who" to give more information about a person.'
   },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "in", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "at", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'that'
   },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "in", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "at", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'whose'
   },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "in", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "at", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'whom'
   },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "in", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "at", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'who'
   },
  ]
export default quiz3data
